The stakes are
Speaker 1: high and we're fighting
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): on MAGA's gonna be your
Speaker 3: number one I
Speaker 3: I'm not the kind of girl to give up just
Speaker 4 (lower-pitched voice): like that. Oh no, not the punches you throw that will break my resolve. If you struggle, I'll continue to evolve. I'm not the
Speaker 3: kind of girl to give up just like that. Oh
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): no. Stay.
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): are high and we're fighting on, MAGA's gonna be your number one,
number one, number one. Every challenge
Speaker 5: you present, I'll overcome. I'll keep
Speaker 3: pushing forward till
the battle
Speaker 3: We'll get back.
Speaker 3: I'm not the kind of girl
Speaker 6: To give up just like that Oh
Speaker 2 (lower-pitched voice): no The stakes are high But we're fighting on Maga's gonna be your number one Number
one Number one
Carrie is one
Speaker 7: of the toughest fighters in our movement. She is a fighter. She's strong and she's good. She's got a great heart, by the way. She is very special. With people like Carrie fighting for Arizona in the Senate, with me in the White House, we will make America great again. God bless Arizona. And Carrie, God bless you.
God bless you.